nodeknockout.com 2018-06-27

# Privacy Policy - Node Knockout

### Last revised on August 16th, 2017

### The Big Picture

Node Knockout as a product is owned by Hackbit and is dedicated to safeguarding your privacy online. The following explains how we will treat information that you may provide to us as you make use of our Site and Services. By accessing our websites (the “Sites”) and accepting the Terms of Service (the “Terms of Service”), you consent to our collection, disclosure, storage and use of certain non-personally-identifying information about you as you use our Sites. We may use this data to better understand our users and build a better service. We can also publish this data, but only if the data will portray a large group of users, not individuals.

We may also ask you to provide personal information, but you’ll always be able to opt out of providing such information.

We can also collect information via cookies, but you can choose not to store these. However, choosing to disable cookies may impact your ability to use our services.

That’s the basic idea, but you must read through the entire Privacy Policy below and agree with all the details before you may use any of our services. This Privacy Policy is effective immediately, meaning that every time you visit our Site or use the Services on our Site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy may change over time. Such modifications will become effective immediately upon their posting to this page. It is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy on a regular basis to inform yourself of any changes that may have been made. Your continued use of any of our Services denotes your acceptance of any such modified terms.

## The Fine Print

### Reuse

This document is based upon the [Automattic Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/) and is licensed under [Creative Commons Attribution Share-Alike License 2.5](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/). Basically, this means that you can use it verbatim or edited, but you must release new versions under the same license and you have to credit the original authors within the edited version (like in parentheses, perhaps!). Automattic is not connected with Hackbit in any way, nor do they sponsor or endorse Hackbit or its use of the work.

Hackbit operates the Node Knockout innovation competition and makes available to users certain services, including our Sites (nodeknockout.com), our blog, our API, and any other software, sites, and services offered by Node Knockout in connection to any of those (taken together, the “Service”). It is Hackbit’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our Sites.

### Users

Like most website operators, Hackbit collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each user request.

Hackbit also collects anonymized information about how users use our Service. Hackbit collects this information for purposes such as quality of service improvement, contact, and feature development / research. From time to time, Hackbit  may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate for promotional, marketing, and public relations purposes.

Hackbit also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Hackbit does not use such information to identify its users and does not disclose such information, other than as described below. We may also collect and use IP addresses to block users who violated our Terms of Service.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain users to the Node Knockout website choose to interact with Hackbit in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Hackbit gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Hackbit collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the users’ interaction with the Services. Hackbit does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Users can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Service-related activities.

Additionally, some interactions, such as posting a comment, may ask for optional personal information. For instance, when posting a comment, you may be asked to provide a website that will be displayed along with a user’s name when the comment is displayed. Supplying such personal information is completely optional and is only displayed for the benefit and the convenience of the user.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Hackbit discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, partners and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to provide Services available at the Sites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, partners and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using the Service, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Hackbit will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors, partners and affiliated organizations, as described above, Hackbit discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Hackbit believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Hackbit, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of the Service and have supplied your email address, Hackbit may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, ask for your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Hackbit and competition-related events. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help support other users. Hackbit takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

Hackbit additionally reserves the right to publish your team name, account username, Node Knockout entries, and certain team and individual profile content on its Sites, blog, and in promotions on third party sites in order to promote the Node Knockout competition. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you are acknowledging and allowing the information in your profile and/or your competition entries and application descriptions to be published byHackbit or otherwise used for advertising and promotional purposes.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the Service each time the visitor returns to the website. Hackbit uses cookies to help it identify and track users, their usage of Hackbit Service, and their Service access preferences. Hackbit users who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Node Knockout website, with the drawback that certain features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Data Storage

Hackbit uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Service. You understand that although you retain full rights to your data, it may be stored on third party storage and transmitted through third party networks.

### Third Party Websites

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information Hackbit collects from you. If you disclose your information to others, such as third party websites that are not affiliated with Hackbit, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of your information. For example, by clicking on a third party advertisement and links embedded into user-generated Content, a third party may receive information such as your IP address. Since Hackbit does not control the privacy policies or conduct of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies and user agreements of those third parties. It is your obligation to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and user agreements of such other websites that you use.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Hackbit may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Hackbit’s sole discretion. Hackbit encourages users to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.

### Questions

If you have question about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
